jobdhundo.com 2014-06-26

# Untitled Page

### Privacy Policy

_jobdhundo's Terms of Use Agreement 1. Eligibility._

  1. _No Gurantee of job_
  2. In some cases we also store ip address in our database and also set cookies in user computers
  3. _We do not charge jobseekers_
  4. _We may or may not charge employers_
  5. _We do not share money with the employers or placement consultants in case they charge you for there services_
  6. We only charge subscription fees, in case if we have given free service to certain employers, then it is free
  7. _In Case of Data Leaks, Software Problem , Server Down. we wont be responsible for any losses if any incur to you, some unwanted things may occur, even if we take precautions about it_
  8. _jobdhundo.com will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access of your personal information._
  9. _Your information is safe with us, we do not misuse or sell your information_
  10. Our Policy may change with or without notice

_For more details, you can contact us using contactus page_

_Additional Discolosures_

  1. _Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site._
  2. _Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet._
  3. _Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the_[ _Google ad and content network privacy policy_ ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)_._

_Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we're unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the_[ _Network Advertising Initiative_ ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)_, or NAI, which suggests the following language for data collection of non-personally identifying information:_

> _We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here._

_You can find additional information in Appendix A of the_[ _NAI Self-Regulatory principles for publishers_ ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/pdfs/NAI_principles.pdf)_(PDF). Please note that the NAI may change this sample language at any time._  
  
---
